Local 1199 Records 5510
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Strikes - Miscellaneous Publications [folder 2 of 2], 1958-1959 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Strikes - Truth Kit, 1962 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Strikes - Locals (Leaflets, Notices, Contracts, etc.) [folder 1 of 6], 1960-1963 (Box 49a, Folder 1)
- Strikes - Locals (Leaflets, Notices, Contracts, etc.) [folder 2 of 6], 1960-1963 (Box 49a, Folder 2)
- Strikes - Locals (Leaflets, Notices, Contracts, etc.) [folder 3 of 6], 1960-1963 (Box 49a, Folder 3)
- Strikes - Locals (Leaflets, Notices, Contracts, etc.) [folder 4 of 6], 1960-1963 (Box 49a, Folder 4)
- Strikes - Locals (Leaflets, Notices, Contracts, etc.) [folder 5 of 6], 1960-1963 (Box 49a, Folder 5)
- Strikes - Locals (Leaflets, Notices, Contracts, etc.) [folder 6 of 6], 1960-1963 (Box 49a, Folder 6)
- A Van-Guard Custodial Service, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Abbet Manor Convalescent Home, 1968-1971 (Box 50, Folder 1a)
- Adams Home, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Adelphi Hospital, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Albert Einstein Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1971 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Albert Einstein Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1971 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Alliance Medical Inns, 1970-1971 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Alps Manor Nursing Home [folder 1 of 3], 1962-1970 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Alps Manor Nursing Home [folder 2 of 3], 1962-1970 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Alps Manor Nursing Home [folder 3 of 3], 1962-1970 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Amsterdam House, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Andrews Janitorial Service, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 10a)
- Animal Medical Center, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Arlington Manor Nursing Home [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1969 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Arlington Manor Nursing Home [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1969 (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Association Residence for Women, 1969-1970 (Box 50, Folder 14)
- Association of Voluntary Lon-Term Care Agencies, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 15)
- Atlantic Maintenance Corporation, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 16)
- Barrie Industries, 1970-1972 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Beekman-Downtown Hospital, 1960-1961 (Box 51, Folder 1a)
- Bel-Air Nursing Home [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1970 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Bel-Air Nursing Home [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1970 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Berkeley Hall Nursing Home [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1970 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Berkeley Hall Nursing Home [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1970 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Beth Abraham Home, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 5a)
- Beth Abraham Hospital [folder 1 of 5], 1959-1970 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Beth Abraham Hospital [folder 2 of 5], 1959-1970 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Beth Abraham Hospital [folder 3 of 5], 1959-1970 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Beth Abraham Hospital [folder 4 of 5], 1959-1970 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Beth Abraham Hospital [folder 5 of 5], 1959-1970 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Beth-El Hospital [folder 1 of 3], 1958-1962 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- Beth-El Hospital [folder 2 of 3], 1958-1962 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Beth-El Hospital [folder 3 of 3], 1958-1962 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- Beth Israel Hospital [folder 1 of 5], 1959-1970 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Beth Israel Hospital [folder 2 of 5], 1959-1970 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Beth Israel Hospital [folder 3 of 5], 1959-1970 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Beth Israel Hospital [folder 4 of 5], 1959-1970 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Beth Israel Hospital [folder 5 of 5], 1959-1970 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Birchwood Nursing Home [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1970 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Birchwood Nursing Home [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1970 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Booth Memorial Hospital, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Broadway Presbyterian Church, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Bronx Eye and Ear Infirmary [folder 1 of 3], 1965-1970 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Bronx Eye and Ear Infirmary [folder 2 of 3], 1965-1970 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Bronx Eye and Ear Infirmary [folder 3 of 3], 1965-1970 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Bronx-Lebanon Hospital, 1959-1968 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Brookdale Hospital Center [folder 1 of 2], 1966-1970 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Brookdale Hospital Center [folder 2 of 2], 1966-1970 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Brooklyn Hospital, 1959-1963 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Brooklyn Cumberland Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1968-1970 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Brooklyn Cumberland Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1968-1970 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Brooklyn Cumberland Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1968-1970 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Brooklyn Cumberland Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1968-1970 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Brooklyn Hebrew Home and Hospital, 1958-1963 (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Brookside Nursing Home [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1970 (Box 54, Folder 9)
- Brookside Nursing Home [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1970 (Box 54, Folder 10)
- Brookwood Convalescent Home, 1968-1970 (Box 54, Folder 11)
- Brunswick Nursing Home, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Buckley Convalescent Home, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 13)
- Caledonian Hospital, 1960-1961 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Calvary Hospital, 1962-1963 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Cedar Manor Nursing Home [folder 1 of 2], 1967-1970 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Cedar Manor Nursing Home [folder 2 of 2], 1967-1970 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Christ Hospital, 1962-1964 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Church Charity Foundation of Long Is., 1972 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Cincinnati Janitorial and Maintenance, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 6a)
- Clara Mass Memorial Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1970 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Clara Mass Memorial Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1970 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Clinton Nursing Home [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1970 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Clinton Nursing Home [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1970 (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Coki Custodial Service, Inc., 1970 (Box 55, Folder 10a)
- 'Colchester Convalescent Home, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 11)
- Columbia University, 1968-1970 (Box 55, Folder 12)
- Community Health Services, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 13)
- Community Hospital of Brooklyn [folder 1 of 2], 1962-1967 (Box 55, Folder 14)
- Community Hospital of Brooklyn [folder 2 of 2], 1962-1967 (Box 55, Folder 15)
- Convalescent Home of New York, 1971-1972 (Box 55, Folder 16)
- Cornell Hall Convalescent Home, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 17)
- County Maintenance Company, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 18)
- Crathall Company, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 19)
- Danbury Pavilion, 1970 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Daughters of Israel Home, 1969-1971 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Daughters of Miriam Home [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1970 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Daughters of Miriam Home [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1970 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Deepdale General Hospital, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Doctor's Hospital, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- Doctor's Hospital, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Doctor Friedman's Nursing Home, 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 8)
- Donnelly Memorial Hospital, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 9)
- Dumont Nursing Home, 1968-1969 (Box 56, Folder 10)
- Dynamic Enterprises, 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 10a)
- East Orange Hospital, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 11)
- Eastern Long Island Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1966-1970 (Box 56, Folder 12)
- Eastern Long Island Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1966-1970 (Box 56, Folder 13)
- Eastern Maintenance Company, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 14)
- Eden Park Convalescent Hospital, 1968-1970 (Box 56, Folder 15)
- Elizabeth Manor Nursing Home [folder 1 of 4], 1965-1970 (Box 56, Folder 16)
- Elizabeth Manor Nursing Home [folder 2 of 4], 1965-1970 (Box 56, Folder 17)
- Elmwood Manor Nursing Home [folder 3 of 4], 1965-1970 (Box 56, Folder 18)
- Elmwood Manor Nursing Home [folder 4 of 4], 1965-1970 (Box 56, Folder 19)
- Englewood Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1967-1970 (Box 56, Folder 20)
- Englewood Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1967-1970 (Box 56, Folder 21)
- Evangelical Deaconess Hospital, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 22)
- Evangelical Home for the Aged, 1968-1970 (Box 56, Folder 23)
- Ewing Parkway Nursing Home, 1970 (Box 56, Folder 24)
- Fitkin Hospital (Box 56, Folder 25)
- Flower and Fifth Avenue Hospital [folder 1 of 6], 1959-1968 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Flower and Fifth Avenue Hospital [folder 2 of 6], 1959-1968 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Flower and Fifth Avenue Hospital [folder 3 of 6], 1959-1968 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Flower and Fifth Avenue Hospital [folder 4 of 6], 1959-1968 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Flower and Fifth Avenue Hospital [folder 5 of 6], 1959-1968 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Flower and Fifth Avenue Hospital [folder 6 of 6], 1959-1968 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Flushing Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1963-1970 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Flushing Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1963-1970 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Freeport Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1970 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Freeport Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1970 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- French Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1962-1970 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- French Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1962-1970 (Box 58, Folder 6)
- French Hospital, 1962-1970 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Gouverneur Clinic, 1963-1967 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Gracie Square Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1963-1970 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Gracie Square Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1963-1970 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Graham Home for Old Ladies, 1970-1971 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Grand Central Hospital, 1959-1963 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Greenpoint, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Greenwood Nursing Home, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Harlem Eye and Ear Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1969 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Harlem Eye and Ear Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1969 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Hartford Convalescent Home, 1969-1970 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Hawkes Ambulance Service, Inc., 1961-1963 (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Haym Salomon Home [folder 1 of 3], 1961-1970 (Box 59, Folder 12)
- Haym Salomon Home [folder 2 of 3], 1961-1970 (Box 59, Folder 13)
- Haym Salomon Home [folder 3 of 3], 1961-1970 (Box 59, Folder 14)
- Health Care Nursing Centers, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Hebrew Convalescent Home, 1962-1963 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Hebrew Home and. Hospital for Chronic Sic] [folder 1 of 3], 1960-1962 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Hebrew Home and. Hospital for Chronic Sic] [folder 2 of 3], 1960-1962 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Hebrew Home and. Hospital for Chronic Sic] [folder 3 of 3], 1960-1962 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Hebrew Home and Hospital of N.J. [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1970 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Hebrew Home and Hospital of N.J. [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1970 (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Hebrew Institute of Long Island, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- Helene Fuld Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1970 (Box 60, Folder 9)
- Helene Fuld Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1970 (Box 60, Folder 10)
- Hempstead General Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1970 (Box 60, Folder 11)
- Hempstead General Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1970 (Box 60, Folder 12)
- High Ridge Convalescent Home, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Hilaire Nursing Home [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1972 (Box 60, Folder 14)
- Hilaire Nursing Home [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1972 (Box 60, Folder 15)
- Hilldale Extend-A-Care Centers, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 16)
- Hillside Hospital, 1971-1972 (Box 60, Folder 17)
- Homes Negotiations and Arbitrations, 1961-1963 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Home and Hospital Daughters of Israel [folder 1 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Home and Hospital Daughters of Israel [folder 2 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Home and Hospital Daughters of Israel [folder 3 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Home and Hospital Daughters of Israel [folder 4 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Home and Hospital Daughters of Israel [folder 1 of 4], 1959-1971 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Home and Hospital Daughters of Jacob [folder 2 of 4], 1960-1970 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Home and Hospital Daughters of Jacob [folder 3 of 4], 1960-1970 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- Home and Hospital Daughters of Jacob [folder 4 of 4], 1960-1970 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Home and Hospital Daughters of Jacob, 1960-1970 (Box 61, Folder 10)
- Home of Old Israel [folder 1 of 2], 1959-1968 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- Home of Old Israel [folder 2 of 2], 1959-1968 (Box 61, Folder 12)
- Home for Aged and Infirm Hebrews, 1962-1963 (Box 61, Folder 12a)
- Home for Old Men and Aged Couples, 1970-1972 (Box 61, Folder 13)
- Home of Old Israel, 1960 (Box 61, Folder 13a)
- Home of the Sages of Israel, 1970-1972 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Home-Sons & Daughters of Israel, 1961-1962 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Hospital for Joint Diseases [folder 1 of 3], 1961-1971 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Hospital for Joint Diseases [folder 2 of 3], 1961-1971 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Hospital for Joint Diseases [folder 3 of 3], 1961-1971 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Hospital Parking Company of America [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1969 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Hospital Parking Company of America [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1969 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- House of the Holy Comforter [folder 1 of 3], 1963-1972 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- House of the Holy Comforter [folder 2 of 3], 1963-1972 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- House of the Holy Comforter [folder 3 of 3], 1963-1972 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- Inland Service Inc., 1970 (Box 62, Folder 8a)
- Interboro Hospital, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Institute for Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1960-1962 (Box 62, Folder 10)
- Irvington Nursing Home [folder 1 of 3], 1962-1970 (Box 62, Folder 11)
- Irvington Nursing Home [folder 2 of 3], 1962-1970 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Irvington Nursing Home [folder 3 of 3], 1962-1970 (Box 62, Folder 13)
- Israel Golden Age Housing Foundation, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 14)
- Israel Senior Citizens Housing Corp., 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 15)
- Jacobi Hospital (and Coffee Shop) [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1970 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Jacobi Hospital (and Coffee Shop) [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1970 (Box 63, Folder 1a)
- Jamaica Hospital, 1962-1963 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Jersey City Medical Center [folder 1 of 2], 1967-1972 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Jersey City Medical Center [folder 2 of 2], 1967-1972 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Jewish Association for Services for the Aged, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Jewish Chronic Disease Hospital [folder 1 of 3], 1960-1965 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Jewish Chronic Disease Hospital [folder 2 of 3], 1960-1965 (Box 63, Folder 7)
- Jewish Chronic Disease Hospital [folder 3 of 3], 1960-1965 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Jewish Home and Hospital for Aged [folder 1 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 63, Folder 9)
- Jewish Home and Hospital for Aged [folder 2 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 63, Folder 10)
- Jewish Home and Hospital for Aged [folder 3 of 3], 1965-1971 (Box 63, Folder 11)
- Jewish Hospital of Brooklyn [folder 1 of 7], 1959-1970 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Jewish Hospital of Brooklyn [folder 2 of 7], 1959-1970 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Jewish Hospital of Brooklyn [folder 3 of 7], 1959-1970 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Jewish Hospital of Brooklyn [folder 4 of 7], 1959-1970 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Jewish Hospital of Brooklyn [folder 5 of 7], 1959-1970 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Jewish Hospital of Brooklyn [folder 6 of 7], 1959-1970 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Jewish Hospital of Brooklyn [folder 7 of 7], 1959-1970 (Box 64, Folder 7)
- Jewish Hospital-Rehabilitation Center of N.J., 1968-1971 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Jewish Institute for Geriatric Care, 1971-1972 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Jewish Memorial Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1972 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Jewish Memorial Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1972 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Kings Highway Hospital, 1957 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Kingsbrook Jewish Medical Center [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1972 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Kingsbrook Jewish Medical Center [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1972 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Kinney Service Company, 1964 (Box 65, Folder 7a)
- Kleen-Rite Janitorial Service, 1969-1970 (Box 65, Folder 7b)
- Knickerbocker Hospital [folder 1 of 3], 1959-1972 (Box 65, Folder 8)
- Knickerbocker Hospital [folder 2 of 3], 1959-1972 (Box 65, Folder 9)
- Knickerbocker Hospital [folder 3 of 3], 1959-1972 (Box 65, Folder 10)
- Lakeside Hospital, 1964-1965 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Laura Parker Nursing Home [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1970 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Laura Parker Nursing Home [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1970 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Lawrence Hospital (Box 66, Folder 3a)
- League of Voluntary Hospital and Homes, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Lemberger Home for the Aged [folder 1 of 2], 1961-1967 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Lemberger Home for the Aged [folder 2 of 2], 1961-1967 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Lemberger Geriatric Institute, 1968-1972 (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Lenox Hill Hospital [folder 1 of 5], 1959-1971 (Box 66, Folder 8)
- Lenox Hill Hospital [folder 2 of 5], 1959-1971 (Box 66, Folder 9)
- Lenox Hill Hospital [folder 3 of 5], 1959-1971 (Box 66, Folder 10)
- Lenox Hill Hospital [folder 4 of 5], 1959-1971 (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Lenox Hill Hospital [folder 5 of 5], 1959-1971 (Box 66, Folder 12)
- Lincoln Hospital, 1967-1971 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Long Beach Memorial Hospital, 1962-1963 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Long Island College Hospital, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Long Island Doctor's Hospital, 1961-1972 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Long Island General Hospital, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- Long Island Jewish Hospital [folder 1 of 3], 1959-1967 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Long Island Jewish Hospital [folder 2 of 3], 1959-1967 (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Long Island Jewish Hospital [folder 3 of 3], 1959-1967 (Box 67, Folder 8)
- Long Island Jewish Medical Center, 1960-1972 (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Long Island Nursing Home, 1969-1970 (Box 67, Folder 10)
- Lutheran Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1965 (Box 67, Folder 11)
- Lutheran Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1965 (Box 67, Folder 12)
- Lutheran Medical Center [folder 1 of 3], 1962-1972 (Box 67, Folder 13)
- Lutheran Medical Center [folder 2 of 3], 1962-1972 (Box 67, Folder 14)
- Lutheran Medical Center [folder 3 of 3], 1962-1972 (Box 67, Folder 15)
- Maimonides Hospital [folder 1 of 6], 1957-1973 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- Maimonides Hospital [folder 2 of 6], 1957-1973 (Box 68, Folder 2)
- Maimonides Hospital [folder 3 of 6], 1957-1973 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Maimonides Hospital [folder 4 of 6], 1957-1973 (Box 68, Folder 4)
- Maimonides Hospital [folder 5 of 6], 1957-1973 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- Maimonides Hospital [folder 6 of 6], 1957-1973 (Box 68, Folder 6)
- Manchester Memorial Hospital, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 7)
- Manhasset Medical Center [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1972 (Box 68, Folder 8)
- Manhasset Medical Center [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1972 (Box 68, Folder 9)
- Manhattan Eye, Ear and Throat Hospital [folder 1 of 3], 1959-1972 (Box 68, Folder 10)
- Manhattan Eye, Ear and Throat Hospital [folder 2 of 3], 1959-1972 (Box 68, Folder 11)
- Manhattan Eye, Ear and Throat Hospital [folder 3 of 3], 1959-1972 (Box 68, Folder 12)
- Mary Manning Walsh Home, 1970-1972 (Box 68, Folder 13)
- Medi Center of America, 1971-1972 (Box 68, Folder 14)
- Meadowbrook Nursing Home, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 15)
- Memorial Center for Women, 1969-1972 (Box 68, Folder 16)
- Memorial Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1959-1963 (Box 68, Folder 17)
- Memorial Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1959-1963 (Box 68, Folder 18)
- Menorah Home and Hospital, 1959-1962 (Box 68, Folder 19)
- Methodist Hospital, 1962 (Box 68, Folder 20)
- Middlesex General Hospital, 1972 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Milford Heights Nursing Home, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Misericordia Hospital, 1962 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Modern Maintenance, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Montclair Community Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1968-1970 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Montclair Community Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1968-1970 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Montclair Nursing Home [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1972 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- Montclair Nursing Home [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1972 (Box 69, Folder 8)
- Montefoire Hospital [folder 1 of 14], 1958-1972 (Box 69, Folder 9)
- Montefoire Hospital [folder 2 of 14], 1958-1972 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Montefoire Hospital [folder 3 of 14], 1958-1972 (Box 69, Folder 11)
- Montefoire Hospital [folder 4 of 14], 1958-1972 (Box 69, Folder 12)
- Montefoire Hospital [folder 5 of 14], 1958-1972 (Box 69, Folder 13)
- Montefoire Hospital [folder 6 of 14], 1958-1972 (Box 69, Folder 14)
- Montefoire Hospital [folder 7 of 14], 1958-1972 (Box 69, Folder 15)
- Montefoire Hospital [folder 8 of 14], 1958-1972 (Box 69, Folder 16)
- Montefoire Hospital [folder 9 of 14], 1958-1972 (Box 69, Folder 17)
- Montefoire Hospital [folder 10 of 14], 1958-1972 (Box 69, Folder 18)
- Montefoire Hospital [folder 11 of 14], 1958-1972 (Box 69, Folder 19)
- Montefoire Hospital [folder 12 of 14], 1958-1972 (Box 69, Folder 20)
- Montefoire Hospital [folder 13 of 14], 1958-1972 (Box 69, Folder 21)
- Montefoire Hospital [folder 14 of 14], 1958-1972 (Box 69, Folder 22)
- Morrisania City Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1966-1971 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Morrisania City Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1966-1971 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Mt. Morris Park Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1959-1964 (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Mt. Morris Park Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1959-1964 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Mt. Sinai Hospital [folder 1 of 13], 1959-1972 (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Mt. Sinai Hospital [folder 2 of 13], 1959-1972 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Mt. Sinai Hospital [folder 3 of 13], 1959-1972 (Box 70, Folder 7)
- Mt. Sinai Hospital [folder 4 of 13], 1959-1972 (Box 70, Folder 8)
- Mt. Sinai Hospital [folder 5 of 13], 1959-1972 (Box 70, Folder 9)
- Mt. Sinai Hospital [folder 6 of 13], 1959-1972 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Mt. Sinai Hospital [folder 7 of 13], 1959-1972 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Mt. Sinai Hospital [folder 8 of 13], 1959-1972 (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Mt. Sinai Hospital [folder 9 of 13], 1959-1972 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Mt. Sinai Hospital [folder 10 of 13], 1959-1972 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Mt. Sinai Hospital [folder 11 of 13], 1959-1972 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- Mt. Sinai Hospital [folder 12 of 13], 1959-1972 (Box 71, Folder 7)
- Mt. Sinai Hospital [folder 13 of 13], 1959-1972 (Box 71, Folder 8)
- Neustadter Home, 1968-1972 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- New Brunswick Nursing Home, 1964-1967 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- New Frontier Hall Convalescent Home, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- New Jersey Home & Hospital, 1963-1960 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- NYC Health and Hospital Corp., 1972 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- N.Y. Convalescent Home, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- New York Infirmary [folder 1 of 3], 1959-1971 (Box 72, Folder 7)
- New York Infirmary [folder 2 of 3], 1959-1971 (Box 72, Folder 8)
- New York Infirmary [folder 3 of 3], 1959-1971 (Box 72, Folder 9)
- New York Hospital, 1959-1963 (Box 72, Folder 10)
- N.Y. University Medical Center [folder 1 of 4], 1959-1972 (Box 72, Folder 11)
- N.Y. University Medical Center [folder 2 of 4], 1959-1972 (Box 72, Folder 12)
- N.Y. University Medical Center [folder 3 of 4], 1959-1972 (Box 72, Folder 13)
- N.Y. University Medical Center [folder 4 of 4], 1959-1972 (Box 72, Folder 14)
- Newark Beth Israel Hospital, 1966-1972 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Newark Gardens Convalescent Sanitarium [folder 1 of 4], 1961-1971 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Newark Gardens Convalescent Sanitarium [folder 2 of 4], 1961-1971 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Newark Gardens Convalescent Sanitarium [folder 3 of 4], 1961-1971 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Newark Gardens Convalescent Sanitarium [folder 4 of 4], 1961-1971 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- North Jersey Homes & Hospital, 1963-1960 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- Northern Westchester Hospital, 1972 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- Northfield Manor Nursing Home, 1970-1972 (Box 73, Folder 8)
- Orange Hospital Center, 1960-1967 (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Orange Memorial Hospital, 1967-1972 (Box 73, Folder 10)
- Parkway Hospital, 1963 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Parkway Nursing Home [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1968 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Parkway Nursing Home [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1968 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- Pelham Bay General Hospital, 1961 (Box 74, Folder 4)
- Peninsula General Hospital [folder 1 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Peninsula General Hospital [folder 2 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Peninsula General Hospital [folder 3 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- Peninsula General Hospital [folder 4 of 4], 1962-1971 (Box 74, Folder 8)
- Pine Acres Nursing Home [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1971 (Box 74, Folder 9)
- Pine Acres Nursing Home [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1971 (Box 74, Folder 10)
- Pine Haven Nursing Home, 1965-1967 (Box 74, Folder 11)
- Polyclinic Hospital [folder 1 of 2], 1961-1962 (Box 74, Folder 12)
- Polyclinic Hospital [folder 2 of 2], 1961-1962 (Box 74, Folder 13)
- Pompton Lakes Nursing Home, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 14)
- Pond Point Hospital, 1968-1972 (Box 74, Folder 15)
- Presbyterian Hospital, 1963 (Box 74, Folder 16)
- Princeton Nursing Home, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 17)
- Prospect Gardens, 1969-1970 (Box 74, Folder 18)
- Prospect Heights Hospital, 1959 (Box 74, Folder 19)